europasports.com 2006-12-23

# Europa Sports Products >> Privacy Policy

Europa Sports Products values its customers and respects their privacy. We collect customer information to validate you as a legal reseller. Europa Sports Products recognizes that it must maintain and use customer information responsibly. We do not sell or rent the information you provide to us online to third parties. However, we do share your information with third parties under certain circumstances.

This policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, click here to contact Europa Sports Products customer service via [email](mailto:customerservice@europasports.com), call us at 1-800-447-4795.

If our information practices change in the future, we will let you know by posting the policy changes on our Web site.

##### Collection and Use of Information

Our Site's registration forms, surveys and contests require you to give us contact information (like your name and email address), and demographic information (like your zip code, state, company name,..). We use this information to verify you as a legal reseller. We keep this information on file and allow you to maintain it's accuracy here. You can also opt in or out of direct marketing campaigns.

We use this information to facilitate your orders when you use the online catalog to send orders in to your sales representative. We may also use your email address or phone number to contact you regarding an order.

We do not share your information with third parties.

##### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that Web sites often store on your computer's hard drive when you visit their sites. A cookie may contain information (such as a unique user ID), that is used to track the pages of the sites you've visited. We use cookies but do not store personally identifiable information in your cookie.

We use cookies to make your visits to our Web site more personal by remembering your preferences if you have been to our site before. We use cookies remember that you are logged in so that you do not have to enter a password to access every page. 

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you turn off cookies, though, you will not be able to access our online catalog or access any of our customer only sections of the Web site. Nor will we be able to recognize you as a signed up user to allow you access to your account information.

##### Log Files

We also use log files to track and maintain the identity of the Web site you visited immediately prior to ours to further improve our site design. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other Web sites.

We also use log files to track your progress through our Site in order to improve site navigation and ease of use. We collect browser types, operating system types, etc. to again improve your experience on our Site.

##### Your Private Information

Our registration forms may require financial information (like your account number, resale certificate number, or tax ID) as well. We do not request Credit Card numbers. This information is only used internally and not shared with any third parties.

##### Your Contact Information

Your contact information is used to contact you when necessary in connection with transactions entered into by you on our Site. We also use customer contact information we collect in order to send you information and offers from our company and promotional material from some of our partners. You can opt in or out of this by updating your profile. We carefully select the information we send and make sure that it offers real value to you, such as discounts, exclusive offers or information regarding new products available to the industry.

##### Demographic Information 

We use this information to tailor our Site to the interests of our users.

##### Other Sites/Third Party Vendors and their Privacy Policies

This Site may contain links to other Sites. Europa Sports Products is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites or for the privacy policies and practices of other third parties.  

##### Your Disclosures in Chats, Message Boards, Forums, etc,...

This Site may make available to its users chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups. Please remember that any information you disclose in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.  

##### Our Security Precautions 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.   

##### Update Your Member's Profile Information

This Site gives users the opportunity to change and/or modify information you have provided to us through your Online Registration Process. You may access your profile here.  

##### Updating Your Member's Profile Information

Changing or updating your data through the your profile will only change the data only in our Customer's database, but will not change or delete information which we may have collected within our transactions database.

##### Deleting Your Member's Profile Information

To delete your account or any information regarding your account must either be done through the Update Account process or done over the phone when contacting our Customer Service Department (1.800.447.4795). This will delete the requested information from your account and may in turn revoke your Europasports.com Member's privileges. 

#####  Register

Register to gain access to our online catalog.

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy statement, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at **[web@EuropaSports.com](mailto:web@europasports.com).**

You can also send us mail to:
